[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 15]
If the two halves of the Baize Token are merged outside our bodies,
can it be returned
to Baize Goddess?
Brat,
you finally said that.
So you know your place.
I thought you were going to keep it for yourself.
♫A lone boat drifts through the world♫
I don't want it.
♫The heart feels bitter, then sweet♫
The responsibility is too heavy.
♫Can't distinguish night from day♫
I just want to be a free great demon.
Go wherever I want
and do whatever I want
♫At the edge of the dreamscape♫
without a care in the world.
♫Someone is longing for♫
♫Softly calling for♫
♫A past that can't be brought back♫
Activating the Constellation Formation
requires two Mountain Gods.
By then,
Zhu Yin and I
will assist them
from the side.
You two
just need to
activate the Baize Token in the formation.
Great.
The Wilderness can be saved.
Sister Pei.
Zhuo is still up there trying to cheer Jiu up.
Jiu is too young.
He doesn't understand that it wasn't personal.
It's just that the situation was perilous
and we had to be careful.
You're right.
But the plan of the Demon Hunting Bureau
was indeed leaked to the Chongwu Camp.
So I don't think
Mr. Situ is mistaken
about the mole.
By the way, Sister Pei,
where are you going?
The Chongwu Camp is great at tracking,
especially tracking demons.
They've never failed at it.
Maybe
they tracked Zhao Yuanzhou here.
For safety's sake,
I'll go check the perimeter.
I'm just a kid.
It's easy to cheer me up.
Just some candy
or a pat on the head will do.
Did you just throw it at me?
Don't you like fruit?
Grandpa.
All these years,
you've been protecting Mount Kunlun,
which is on the brink of destruction.
Don't you feel tired?
I do,
but it's my duty.
Boy,
do you know what it takes
to become the Mountain God?
One needs to have divine blood
and be very powerful.
Wrong.
What makes you the Mountain God
is your determination
to protect the Wilderness.
Boy.
Whether to stay in the Wilderness
or go to the mortal world
is your decision
to make.
No matter what your choice is,
I'll support you.
In this world,
there are thousands of paths
leading to your destination.
As for which one is right for you,
you have to find out yourself.
Sure enough.
You wouldn't waste
the fruit Mr. Zhuo gave you.
None of your business.
Looks like Zhuo messed up his apology.
He's really stupid.
I called him stupid.
Why are you angry?
If they had suspected you,
would you be angry?
As long as I have a clear conscience,
I don't care
what others think of me.
But rumors are scary.
Born in the Wilderness,
you naturally don't know what rumors can do.
So it's better to be a demon.
I don't need to guess what others think.
Where are you going?
I'm going to do something bad.
To find some demons and have fun.
When did Little Bunny learn
to speak sarcastically?
You've rubbed off on him.
It's just the two of us now.
Tell me.
Tell you what?
What day is tomorrow?
What will happen?
You looked worried just now.
There's definitely something on your mind.
Lady Goddess, I didn't expect you
to pay so much attention to me.
I'm so touched.
I have no choice.
To make the Baize Token complete,
we must be of one mind.
You once asked me
why I was controlled by malicious energy.
You didn't answer me then.
The night I lost control,
it was a blood moon.
Blood moon?
On a blood moon,
malicious energy is the most strong.
With so much malicious energy in me,
if I can't control it,
I'll be consumed by it.
You mean…
Tomorrow night…
Are you worried
you may lose control again?
On that blood moon,
malicious energy took control of me,
and I lost consciousness.
In a trance,
I killed many people from the Demon Hunting Bureau.
Logically speaking,
the blood moon would last the whole night.
But somehow,
that night,
I regained my sanity very soon.
When I woke up,
I was already inside the White Emperor Tower.
[The Wilderness]
I never understood the reason.
Now that I think about it,
your master, Zhao Wan'er,
must have sent half of the Baize Token
into my body
to suppress the uncontrollable malicious energy.
Otherwise,
the consequences would've been unimaginable.
You went through so much trouble
to help me find the Baize Token
just to...
To end my life.
My wish can be fulfilled,
and you can get the world rid of a great demon.
Do you know why your master, Zhao Wan'er,
gave her brother's name
to me?
No.
I asked her that question.
She told me
because I was like a prisoner
in a sea of bitterness.
Death
is my only escape.
If I lose control again tomorrow,
you must kill me with the Baize Token.
Boys,
wait a little longer.
It's about time to hunt.
If…
the Baize Token stays in your body,
you won't be consumed by malicious energy
and lose control, will you?
No.
But to activate the Constellation Formation,
the Baize Token must be merged outside my body.
The formation will be finished by noon.
After that,
can't we divide the Baize Token into two
and send a half back into your body?
It's better than letting you lose control
and start a killing spree.
You can actually…
sympathize with a demon?
Demons are born aggressive.
That's why they need to be disciplined.
Demons wish to be accepted by humans.
We also wish
demons wouldn't hurt us.
But there are always demons disguised as humans
causing chaos in the mortal world
and spreading fear.
You always say you can't hate the Wilderness more,
but actually,
you love it more than anyone else,
don't you?
I…
What's wrong?
It's happened a lot recently.
It's not the first time.
What's wrong with you?
It's all because of the contract you made me sign.
Which term did you violate?
The one that says
I shall stay with you willingly
as your colleague.
You broke the contract.
You deserve the pain.
You're so cruel.
No.
I'm pretty and kind,
okay?
Since you're so pitiful,
I'll teach you a spell
to relieve your pain.
There's such a spell?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Form is indeed emptiness,
emptiness indeed form.
It's from the Heart Sutra.
Read it now and then.
Clear the bad ideas
from your mind.
Look at Zhuo
and then you.
You're not in his league.
Zhuo is like your brother.
Of course we're different.
You assume that Zhuo is like a brother to me.
I don't think he'll agree.
What else could he be?
Who knows?
After all, Zhuo is so handsome
that he's the dreamboat of countless girls in Tiandu.
And he and I grew up together.
Listen.
What?
The sound of jealousy.
I know I can't persuade you,
but I believe
that one day
you'll meet the person who makes you want to live.
♫Footsteps echo, one by one♫
♫Sorrows scattered, lost to the wind♫
♫Not forgetting, nor dwelling on♫
♫The way back home♫
♫With strong will♫
♫I slowly carve out♫
♫Growth♫
♫Turning back♫
♫I find you still in that familiar place♫
♫Waiting there♫
Ms. Pei, you're really something.
You actually found me here.
Jiu.
Mr. Zhuo, you're so diligent.
It's so late. Instead of sleeping,
you're secretly practicing swordsmanship.
The sooner I learn it,
the sooner I can kill you
to fulfill your wish.
It's a win-win.
Of course I need to practice hard.
Practice makes perfect,
but if you do it wrongly
and get ahead of yourself,
you'll hurt yourself.
None of your business.
I taught you this.
Of course it's my business.
Who is he?
Your ancestor,
Bingyi,
the first master of the Cloud Light Sword.
The sword technique just now...
Was the very one Bingyi used
to slay Ying Long.
Can it kill you?
Ying Long was much stronger than I am.
It was an ancient great demon
that could kill Ying Long,
so of course, it could kill me too.
Take your time to understand it.
Why are you teaching me?
Didn't I already tell you?
I want you to kill me.
You're lying.
I'm not.
When you made the oath with me
in the dungeon back then,
you truly weren't lying.
I'll teach you the true way to use the Cloud Light Sword.
Then...
Kill me.
Back then, you were consumed
by a desire for death,
and your eyes were void of light.
But now,
I can see that
you no longer wish to die.
Is it because of Wen Xiao?
I've always found the Wilderness
to be cold and lifeless.
Living for a thousand years has been dull.
But after wandering the mortal world a few times,
I found that mortal hearts
have their own charm.
So, for now, I don't want to die.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
trust me.
The further you go,
the less you'll want to die.
No matter how well you treat Wen Xiao,
I've already sworn a deadly oath
that one day,
I will kill you with my sword.
If I truly grasp the essence of the Cloud Light Sword
and master the technique in the illusion,
won't you regret it?
No, I won't.
I don't understand.
Why?
Since you no longer want to die,
why are you still teaching me?
♫Footsteps echo, one by one♫
Living with contradictions—
doesn't it make you uncomfortable?
♫Sorrows scattered, lost to the wind♫
Many people in this world
♫Not forgetting, nor dwelling on♫
live with contradictions.
I'm not the only one
♫The way back home♫
heading south without hesitation,
♫With strong will♫
yet there's always a voice in my mind
♫I slowly carve out♫
calling me to look north.
♫Growth♫
♫Turning back♫
Mr. Zhuo,
♫I find you still in that familiar place♫
tomorrow's magic formation
will determine the survival of the Wilderness.
♫Waiting there♫
If anything unexpected happens,
I hope you can...
If there's danger,
I'll ensure Wen Xiao's safety.
I meant me.
You?
A thousand-year-old great demon
needs my protection?
How embarrassing.
How is that possible?
What I meant is that I hope you live well.
♫Sunset♫
♫Old tiles♫
I don't need you to tell me that.
♫Manjusaka♫
You owe me a life.
As long as you're alive,
♫A single wing♫
♫Struggles to♫
I won't die before you.
♫Maintain a dual balance♫
Fine.
Then please keep your word
and let me die first.
Where's Jiu?
He should be with Ms. Pei.
That's good.
Ying Lei,
come with me to stand guard outside,
so Wen Xiao and the others can focus on their spellcasting.
No problem.
It's noon now.
Once the formation begins,
it cannot be interrupted.
Are you
all prepared?
Yes.
Finally.
Zhu Yin,
start the formation!
The stars align
to stabilize the universe.
Protect!
All sources converge.
Yin and Yang reflect each other,
and heaven and earth work in harmony.
Unite.
What's going on?
Zhu Yin,
you...
I knew there was something wrong with you.
The Star Formation requires two Mountain Gods to complete it.
Ying Zhao,
it's useless for you to hold on alone.
Stop dreaming of saving the Wilderness.
It's you?
Mr. Zhuo,
we meet again.
No, something's wrong.
They are not humans,
nor demons.
They are...
Ying Lei.
Fall back behind me.
Fish scales?
That's Henggong fish from the Wilderness!
Henggong fish?
The scales of Ran Yi are incredibly rare.
Here, take these.
Maybe later,
when you develop a new divine medicine,
they'll be useful.
These scales
are so hard and sharp.
They could even be used as hidden weapons.
There's something more powerful.
Good stuff.
I once saw a monster in the Wilderness
called Henggong fish.
Its scales are as hard as steel,
impervious to blades and spears.
Sounds like
it would make excellent armor.
Its whole body is red,
and its roar can shatter mountains and stone.
Could it be...
Zheng?
What you're describing
are all monsters from the Wilderness.
But they are human.
Are you insane?
How could these be human?
Zhu Yin,
why are you doing this?
Because he and I
share the same goal.
Ying Zhao,
long time no see.
These despicable tricks again.
The number of times you can possess others is limited.
Li Lun,
you use forbidden arts so recklessly.
Are you, like me,
set on death?
Zhu Yin,
you, a dignified Mountain God,
have fallen so low as to conspire with Li Lun, like a pack of wolves.
A pack of wolves?
Now, you even use us demons
as comparisons in insults.
Good for you,
Zhao Yuanzhou.
You've been living in the mortal world
under someone else's name for so long
that you've forgotten
you're a notorious great demon,
Zhu Yan, haven't you?
Your goal is to
bring ruin to the Wilderness
and lead all demons to their deaths, isn't it?
You're wrong.
It's to allow all living beings in the Wilderness
to freely travel between the two worlds,
no longer confined to this
desolate,
barren land.
♫The trees and grass of the world sway with the wind♫
♫Beneath the bodhi tree, dust gathers♫
♫Who truly decides fate's design?♫
♫Vividly painted in black and white♫
♫It's water under the bridge♫
♫The moon sheds her light on my heart♫
♫The good old days are gone for good like that lantern in my dream♫
Master once said,
"It's impolite not to reciprocate."
♫See immortals enter Penglai♫
Since I ate your apple,
[Book of Rites]
I'll gift you
♫The northern wind blows from beyond the mountains♫
this Book of Rites in return.
♫Along the icy river, it drifts into my dreams♫
♫Drinking wine at the Tongque Terrace♫
♫Even the stars feel close enough to touch♫
I am the keeper of this temple.
♫Life and death happen in an instant, but love and hate can endure for a long time♫
Do you even know
which god you're worshipping?
♫Beyond cause and effect♫
This is Mountain God,
Zhu Yin.
♫The heavens endure, the world remains eternal♫
Oh.
I know.
Zhu Yin is actually the Torch Dragon, right?
♫Rock and moss♫
People say
the Torch Dragon has great powers.
It controls celestial phenomena
and can move mountains and rivers with its breath.
♫Are watching♫
♫A lone boat drifts through the vast world, vanishing into mist♫
Little scholar,
while he may be powerful,
♫Its sound fading away♫
he can't control
whether or not
you achieve top honors in the imperial examination.
♫I wish♫
♫The sorrow of parting stayed beyond the river, and that we did not share the same mountain and moon♫
I didn't ask Lord Torch Dragon
to make me a Number One Scholar.
♫Deep love, yet fate runs shallow♫
Reading the classics
is to broaden my horizons
and avoid being narrow-minded or self-restrained.
You're here as the temple keeper,
trapped in one place
day after day.
You may not quite understand.
You should
go down the mountain more often.
If you don't understand,
you're welcome to visit me anytime.
I live right at the foot of the mountain,
in the house under the big tree on the west side.
What did Li Lun offer you?
There's no need for an offer.
He and I share the same goal.
Demons are demons.
We will never be accepted by mortals.
What did you add in the tea?
Why did you harm me?
Didn't you say
that studying
is to understand human affairs,
broaden horizons,
and recognize the vastness of the world,
avoiding narrow-mindedness and self-restriction?
But you're a demon.
Why do you want recognition from them?
Baize Goddess
is just a mortal.
On what basis can she set the rules for demons?
Li Lun,
many demons yearn for the mortal world,
but there are also many
who prefer the eternal tranquility of the Wilderness,
living in harmony with the world.
So on what basis can you decide for them
and destroy their homeland?
That's because they are timid and cowardly,
afraid to step into the mortal world.
Zhu Yan,
don't forget.
It was you who led me out of the Wilderness,
allowing me to see the vast world.